govtnic.in 2016-10-21

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
Privacy Policy for GovtNic.In (Blog) – If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by using Contact Us Form.

At GovtNic.In, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, GovtNic.In makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not link to any information that is personally identifiable.

GovtNic.In does not use cookies.

Comment Policy  
If you posting your personal information (like Phone No., Home Address or Email ID) via comment box then we will not responsible for any damage. So practice to send your personal information via “Contact Us” form.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on GovtNic.In.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to GovtNic.In and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/

Some of our advertising, analytics and commenting partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site –  
Google Adsense  
Infolinks  
Chitika  
disqus  
Google Analytics

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on GovtNic.In send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) are also be used by the third-party advertisement networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content that you see.

GovtNic.In has no access to or control over these cookies that used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad-servers for more detail information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. GovtNic.In’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More details information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be finding at the browsers’ respective websites.

Changes to this privacy policy  
GovtNic.In has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site; revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to check frequently this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
